<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 2.4" modifiedIn="OpenLP 2.4" modifiedDate="2017-01-14T20:54:51">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Prayer of The Year of Jubilee of Mercy</title>
    </titles>
    <verseOrder>v1 v2 v3 v4 v5 v6 v7 v8 v9 v10 v11 v12</verseOrder>
    <authors>
      <author>Q.O.A</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>Lord Jesus Christ,<br/>you have taught us <br/>to be merciful<br/>like the heavenly father,<br/>and have told us that <br/>whoever sees you, sees Him.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>Show us your face, <br/>and we will be saved.<br/>Your loving gaze freed <br/>Zacchaeus and Matthew <br/>from being enslaved by money;</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>The adulteress and Magdalene, <br/>from seeking happiness <br/>only in created things;<br/>Made Peter weep <br/>after his betrayal,<br/>and assured Paradise <br/>to the repentant thief.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>Let us hear<br/>as if addressed to <br/>each one of us, <br/>the words that you <br/>spoke to the Samaritan Woman:</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>“If you knew the gift of God!”<br/>You are the visible face <br/>of the invisible Father,<br/>of the God who manifests <br/>his power, <br/>above all by forgiveness <br/>and mercy:</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>Let the Church be your <br/>visible face in the world.<br/>It’s Lord risen and glorified.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines>You willed that your ministers <br/>would also be clothed in weakness, <br/>in order that they <br/>may feel compassion<br/>for those in ignorance and error:</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v8">
      <lines>Let everyone <br/>who approaches them<br/>feel sought after, loved, <br/>and forgiven by God.<br/>Send your Spirit and consecrate <br/>every one of us with its anointing, </lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v9">
      <lines>so that the Jubilee of Mercy<br/>may be a year of Grace <br/>from the Lord,<br/>and your Church<br/>with renewed enthusiasm, </lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v10">
      <lines>may bring good news to the poor,<br/>proclaim liberty to captives<br/>and the oppressed.<br/>And restore sight to the blind.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v11">
      <lines>We ask this of you <br/>Lord Jesus, <br/>through the intercession <br/>of Mary Mother of Mercy;</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v12">
      <lines>You who live and reign <br/>with the father and <br/>the Holy Spirit <br/>forever and ever.<br/>Amen.</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
